Fight the future.
Justice League: The Flashpoint Paradox is a animation, science
fiction, action film directed by Jay Oliva.
The Flash finds himself in a war-torn alternate timeline and teams up with
alternate versions of his fellow heroes to restore the timeline.
Flash / Barry Allen (voice), played by Justin Chambers.
Professor Zoom / Thawne (voice), played by C. Thomas Howell.
Cyborg / Victor Stone (voice), played by Michael B. Jordan.
Batman / Thomas Wayne (voice), played by Kevin McKidd.
Etrigan (voice), played by Dee Bradley Baker.
Lex Luthor (voice), played by Steve Blum.
Justice League: The Flashpoint Paradox is a 2013 American adult animated
superhero film directed by Jay Oliva and written by Jim Krieg.
It is an adaptation of the 2011 comic book crossover
"Flashpoint" by Geoff Johns and Andy Kubert.
The film stars Justin Chambers as Barry Allen / Flash, C.
Thomas Howell as Eobard Thawne / Professor Zoom, Michael B.
Jordan as Victor Stone / Cyborg, Kevin McKidd as Thomas Wayne /
Batman and Cary Elwes as Orin / Arthur Curry / Aquaman.
The film also sees actors reprising roles from other DC animated series, including Kevin Conroy as Bruce Wayne / Batman, Nathan Fillion as Hal Jordan / Green Lantern, Ron
Perlman as Slade Wilson / Deathstroke, Dana Delany as Lois Lane, Vanessa Marshall as Princess Diana / Wonder Woman and Dee Bradley Baker as Etrigan the Demon.
It is the 18th film of the DC Universe Animated Original Movies and
the first film of the DC Animated Movie Universe.
Justice League: The Flashpoint Paradox was released on July 30, 2013, and
was re-released on September 10 as a 2-disc special edition.
The film explores themes of cartoon, time travel,
superhuman, universe, based on graphic novel.
The tone is thought_provoking.